<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="E911_header">Emergency calling notice</string>
    <string name="E911_p1">I understand that the Service allows calls to emergency services number 112. However, I understand that calls will fail if there is a power outage or my Internet or mobile data connections fail. I also understand that neither @~#resellerName#~@ nor any reseller of @~#resellerName#~@ services may be able to provide an emergency organisation with accurate caller location information.</string>
    <string name="E911_p2">With this telephone service, you may have the option to select a phone number that does not correspond to your geographical area. Your @~#resellerName#~@ device will also work anywhere you take it, so long as it has a broadband connection to the Internet, which means you must inform @~#resellerName#~@ or your reseller, or, if applicable, your administrator, of your actual physical address, no matter what telephone number you have, and you or your administrator must update that physical address any time you move.</string>
    <string name="E911_p3">If you do not provide your correct physical location to @~#resellerName#~@ or your reseller when you set up your account, or if you do not update that information when you move your @~#resellerName#~@ device, your emergency calls may be routed to an emergency response center in the wrong location, and/or the wrong address and phone number may be provided to the emergency response center, resulting in potentially lengthy delays in the arrival time of the emergency responders.</string>
    <string name="E911_p4">When you first provide @~#resellerName#~@ or your reseller with your registered location and callback number, and when you update them, there may be a delay in that information becoming available to properly route your calls to the correct emergency response center and to provide the emergency response center with your correct location.</string>
    <string name="E911_p5">As a result of the above, the emergency operator answering the call may not have your call-back number or your exact location, so you must be prepared to provide this information to the operator. Until you give the operator your phone number, they may not be able to call you back or dispatch help if the call is dropped or disconnected, or if you are unable to speak.</string>
    <string name="E911_p6">I authorise @~#resellerName#~@ and/or any reseller of @~#resellerName#~@ services to disclose my name and address to third-parties involved with providing emergency services to me, including but, not limited to, call routers, call centers, and local emergency centers.</string>
    <string name="E911_p7">Neither @~#resellerName#~@ nor your reseller supports messaging services (including but not limited to SMS and MMS) to any emergency services, including accessibility to emergency services by users with disabilities.</string>
    <string name="E911_p8">By clicking on “Accept”, you acknowledge that you have read and understand this Emergency Call disclaimer and the limitations it describes.</string>
    <string name="E911_Accept">Accept</string>
</resources>